Thanks for watching!
Ladies and gentlemen!
Can you see me?
Are you okay?
107 people.
Thank you very much.
Can you see me?
Yes! So...
Let's see...
10,000 YouTube subscribers anniversary live broadcast
It's started!
Yes!
Today is the live stream of the playing, but today we are also doing a live stream on TikTok!
So, if you are a member of the publicity department, please watch whichever you like.
Oh, it's going to have some kind of effects.
This TikTok is amazing!
Congratulations to our 10,000 members! Thank you!
Yes, that's right...
What! Staff!
Hey, you don't have to prepare like that!
Oh, no! Oh, no! What! Are you sure about this cake?
Thank you!
Wow! I'm so surprised!
Maru-chan, you bought it yourself, didn't you?
That's right! I bought the cake myself!
This is the end of the set, but it's a farce.
I bought the cake myself!
I wanted to put a plate on it if I wanted to, but we didn't do plates.
What? That's right! I bought it myself!
So now I want to eat the cake!
I bought the cake myself. I'm sorry, all you can see are the ears.
If you have cake, please have some cake with me, and if you don't have cake, please have some cake with me.
I don't usually buy cake for myself.
I got you a nice cake... you're funny and I like you.
I'll sing after I eat...
First time...
Look, a green tea cake. Have some.
Yay! I bought a cake.
Cake.
Okay, everyone, in honor of Oharu's 10,000 YouTube subscribers...
Congratulations!
Bon appétit!
And is the signal working?
Oh, this is pretty hard.
Bon appétit!
Yes, it's good.
It's good.
Delicious.
I can't see the time.
What time is it?
Uh, yeah.
Okay, 9:00.
I'll start asking around 9:00.
Mmm-hmm.
Yes, Ladurée cake.
I bought it for the first time.
What? It's so good!
Delicious!
The screen looks busy, but, you know, I thought it would be better to distribute it at the same time, so I did it at the same time
Yoo-hoo!
Matcha flavor
Yay!
Oh, how's this?
Yoo-hoo!
We'll be open until 9:30.
What's this? It's delicious!
What's this?
We've got drinks. Two bottles.
Water.
Chocolate eyes.
Oh, my God.
Mmm.
Mwahhh...
Mwahiii!
Here's some water.
That's good.
Mmm.
Moo-hoo!
Snee...
Mnh-mnh.
What's with the sunglasses on your face?
Look at me.
Horse.
Mwah!
We still have 7 more minutes to eat cake, guys!
Thank you for watching.
Yum.
Oh, and the scarf is green too!
One-piece dress today!
I'm craving something salty though!
Oh, I got a hat!
Look, look, look, it looks like a tea pole!
Did you guys have a good time on the tour?
Hito-chan is not here.
Yeah, we're live on YouTube.
Oh!
The tour was fun. Thank you.
Yeah, thanks. I haven't made it yet. Thanks. You should come now.
Oh, he's petting me.Oh, he's stroking me.
I'm so full.
Mmm-mmm-mmm.
I think I'll eat at home
I'm so full
Lately
I've been feeling really...
When I eat something sweet...
I get full very quickly.
Drunken food is infinite.
I don't know...
Are there any of you guys here?
Are there any left?
You're too free. I know, I know. I really am.
I want you to tell me what you had at the Uji. Uji what? Uji?
Matcha rice cakes with strawberries and peaches.
And what else? Tea dumplings? I had a tea dumpling.
You want some? Here you go.
I had tea dumplings, too. What else did I have?
What else did I have?
I forgot.
I forgot what I ate.
What did you eat? Spring...
Hondan chocolates. I had them this morning as a souvenir.
What do you want to eat in Hiroshima? I want to eat fried momiji!
Deep-fried momiji I want deep-fried momiji and sea urchin!
I gave the tsuyashi to Mr. Tsunagari, I gave it to him!
Oh, and I bought some raw yatsuhashi as a souvenir.
What's green tea beef tongue? Is there such a thing?
Oh, yes, there's something sweet... and thankfully, it was catered for.
I had matcha pudding.
So, um... what was that?
What was I going to say?
Oh, yeah, so, um... something sweet... good evening! You're just in time! Thank you!
I haven't eaten any rice cakes.
So I ate too many sweets and my lunch box didn't fit.
Too much food...
I want some chasoba!
I bought some when I was in Shizuoka!
Wow!
Yeah...
Good evening.
I had kobe pirin too.
I ate Kobe Pirin too.
I don't know if I gained weight.
I don't know. But the staff said I've lost weight.
I've lost weight.
Yeah.
They told me.
So I told them to tell me more.
Mmm-hmm.
I'll be in Fukuoka next July 15.
TikTok
I'll be singing and dancing, so eat a lot. Thank you.
I haven't eaten akashiyaki yet.
Thank you for the singing contest!
I won't finish it in 2 minutes, so I'll eat it when I get home.
I'll eat this when I get home.
I'll still love you even if you're a million miles away. I told you.
I want some next time. What does it taste like? Jari-mochi.
I haven't had katsumeshi.
I can't eat momiji manju. Please make it something else.
Oh, really?
Oh, great!
Non-Japanese are watching too!
Happy Birthday, Hiroshima Day!
Yes, this is going to be a pull-out delivery.
Yes, we're going to do a recap afterwards.
Yes, we'll sing afterwards.
I'll sing it later.
I'm eating ekisoba.
Oh, katsumeshi is famous in Kakogawa.
Shall we do it then?
Let's leave the food distribution for now.
Shall we do it? I'll eat it at home.
Shall we do it?
This is the main part.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, Janie Marchi, the red bean paste you just ate is delicious.
I see.
Oh, yes, this is the main part.
Okay, I'll go get my guitar.
I'm home! Cherry tree guitar!
When I eat sweets, my stomach gets upset.
It's delicious, but it makes me sick to my stomach.
I'm going to tune up.
Thank you for watching.
[Guitar sound]
You look so serious.
[Guitar sounds]
Thank you for watching.
OK.
It's not absolute pitch. It's an app.
Okay, we're all done. Let's start from the beginning.
Well, we've come up with a set, but...
I've thought about the set, but I'd like you to make a request on the spot.
I'll check it out and if it's something I can do, I'll do that too.
If you'd like, please make a request.
We can do it on the spot.
If it's a song you can doIf it's a song you can do.
Yay.
I just got here. Thank you.
So, what would you like to hear, your first song?
I've got something for you. What do you want?
Okay, then.
Shall we start with Battle of Time? I've written a song about Battle of Time.
Toki Sen!
Tokugawa's song... Tokugawa's song...
If I do it like this, I'll probably end up with 5 or 6 songs.
Well, I'm bringing my MacBook today.
I'm bringing a MacBook, and I'm doing research on it, isn't that great?
Cool. Thank you. Cool, cool, cool.
Thank you. I've been waiting for you to say that.
Okay, I'll see you later.
I've been doing this since the first song.
I'm getting sick to my stomach.
Okay, here's the main part.
Please listen to it if you like.
Let's start with the first song.
It's called "Super Tokimeki Propaganda Club,
It's a song from the Tokimeki Advertising Department,
I would like to play "Sweet Sweet Days.
Please listen to it.
Please subscribe to our channel.
When I think about that day
Even though it was hot, even though it was sunny, it got a little cold
If you're having trouble
Even if it's cold, even if it's cloudy, you have to do something about it
We can go anywhere.
If we hold hands See, Sweet Sweet Days
Will it disappear someday?
The time that goes by
This is my youth, I'll remember it
Now I want to be here See, Sweet Sweet Days
Because it can't always be there
It's so hard
This is my youth, remember?
I can't say much about it
Wow.
I think I'll just do one chorus.
Thank you very much. I'd like to do more than one song.
I'll make it about one chorus
It's a little difficult, because there's a chord called "Seha". Fireworks!
Yes, I played SSD.
I have some information for guitar players... there's a famous guitar chord website.
If you look up this SSD on the guitar chord site, you'll find a chord called "easy play".
But I'm better at chords played with 2 capos than with capo, so I play 2 capos easily.
I'm better at playing chords with 2 capos, so I play them with 2 capos and easy chords.
So, if you can do it, please refer to the website.
I'll accept requests after I play one more song
Let's see... what would you like?
I'm not sure what's better. tiktok is easier to view on a smartphone.
But if you have a computer, you can watch it on your computer.
I'd be happy if you could watch it on your computer or something.
Office lady time. Office lady time.
I can see the time here. Yay, yay, yay!
It's vertical, so it's really easy to see. I'm glad.
I don't know if I can do this. My mom said I haven't practiced at all.
I was practicing while she was at work.
It's not that I didn't practice while you were at work.
That's right, but...
But there are songs you can play and songs you can't.
So please understand.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Excuses.
Well, um... I received a request...
Um... Aimyeong's song...
I'd like to play Aimyung's song 3636.
I'm sick of it. I'm tired of spending my days with you.
I guess you got bored with the days when you didn't hear any arrangements.
What time did you get home today?
You're sick of my useless early risings and sleeping habits.
I don't know what to do with my hair, and I don't know how to arrange it, and I don't know if I should shut up and get sick of it.
It's hard being a girl.
Oh, I forgot.
I'm going to rust.
I'll go to the delivery box, number 5.
It's the usual code.
I'm in.
Memories of the two of us
The delivery box.
I couldn't open it.
I've closed it so tightly
That door
It doesn't open easily.
Thank you. It's Oharu.
I'm closer to you, really, but I haven't changed my outfit that much.
I usually play a lot of your songs because they have a lot of chords that are easy to play
Harumyon, I'm going to get angry with the adults
Let's see...
I can play "Spring Day" too.
There's so many songs.
There are so many songs
Well...
I, I, I...
I...
I can't speak with typing, but... aren't you typing fast? Surprisingly.
I'm sure everyone expects you to be a slow typist.
But Haru...
No, we can't talk.No, I can't talk.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I bet everyone thinks I'm typing too slow.
You think I'm a slow typist, right, Haru?
Actually, I'm a fast typist.
That's not true. I'm sure it's true.
I'm sure it's true.
I'm sure that's true.
I bet everyone thinks
Haru seems like a slow typist.
Actually, I type fast.
You're surprisingly fast.
I can see why you'd think that.
What am I talking about?
I still think you're late... but that's not true... it's Capo Zero...
Oh, it's on youtube.
I'll take it. I'll take it.
Okay, I'll play "You Don't Listen to Rock 'n' Roll".
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh...
1st floor... ah... I see... contradictory...
핑
Let's hear a song like this
Cue the clapping of hands. Miscellaneous katella.
The two of us to the best of our ability
Lilai
This summer, the dreams of that day dance
I've been holding my breath
Now sit back and listen to the sound of youth
Let's dance to a dry melody
I know you don't listen to rock music
I wanted you to get a little closer to me
Though I don't think you listen to rock music
I've overcome love with songs like this and that
I've overcome love
I know you don't listen to rock music
Thank you for watching
Yes, I like this song very much. Thank you.
I want to do it in spring, too. I want to do a birthday concert someday.
I'd like to do it... but...
I might be able to put down the cost of the sheet music... but... it's a shame...
I'd like to do it someday... that's what I think.
Please send me your requests.
Please do. I don't know if I can do it...
I don't know if I can do it, but you can make a request here.
You're early, early, early!
You're early, you're early
Early, early, early, early
Ah, ah, ah, ah, maybe, maybe I can do it, maybe I can do it
Maybe I've done it before. Maybe I can.
What's wrong? Some people are saying you're cured.
What's wrong?
Well, I don't see most of the comments when I'm playing, so I don't know what's going on.
I think I can do it.
TikTok stopped? Oh, yeah?
Oh, yeah? I'm sorry.
I didn't understand. Forgive me.
Po-yong, it's easy.
I'm fine when I sing. Oh, really? That's good.
You have to keep it simple. It's getting harder and harder to play.
Well, what would you like?
Oh, I give up. Yeah, I give up.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well, have I ever done that before?
Oh, I think I have.
Sometimes I do it at home.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
What was it? Oh, this way.
From the backstrap you were thinking of. Yes, I'll do that too.
Good, good, good, good, good.
Let's see, Mr. Kato.
I think I can do it.
I'll do Yuri's Betelgeuse.
I don't know. It's probably too low. I'll tune it.
It's a star, you told me.
It's like the sky.
Let's just do the chorus. It's low. It's low.
We found each other, we carried each other's hands, and the sky was the same.
We promised that we would shine together.
"Far, far away, Betelgeuse without end...
I'm just holding it together for you, too.
We'll stand shoulder to shoulder, take each other's hands, and keep going.
We swore we wouldn't cry even when times were hard
♪ Far, far away, Betelgeuse without end
You can see it too, can't you? Prayer
It was difficult. It was difficult.
I learned to play the guitar by looking at the sheet music... and I could only play chords that weren't seijas, so thank you very much.
It's not that Seiha chord. Thank you for the song.
I can play the chords that aren't seija, so I'll look at the sheet music and play the ones I think I can play.
So I look at the sheet music and play what I think I can play.
I look at the sheet music and play what I think I can play.
I'm sorry, I can't talk while typing
I can't talk while typing I usually do it in silence when I'm editing
I can't talk. I can't say anything.
I don't even know what I'm saying.
This one is, uh, for beginners, OK.
Okay, this one was requested by a lot of people.
Yes, I'm not an office worker.
I can't be an office worker.Yeah, oh, no, I can't be an office worker, then.
No, you can't be an office worker.
I'm typing while I'm talking.
Oh, I'm done.
Oh, I got a lot of requests for this one, too.
I've been getting a lot of requests for this one, too.
Well, if I can be a constellation...
You're okay with Mr. Bandage, aren't you?
This one...
Mr. Bandage is fine.
I'm going to do "If I could be a constellation".
This was a little difficult.
The clock is almost 6 o'clock and the first star is already there
I want to step on the shadows and lose myself in the night on my way home.
No matter how hard I look for it, there's only one star
From a heart billions of light-years away, it shines so brightly
I don't want you to be loved by everyone, but I'm all alone with you.
If I could gather with you and become a constellation, a wish for a moment on a starry night
Twinkling, shimmering, trembling signals
If I could gather with you and become a constellation, I'd look up at the sky and point my finger at you
Don't untie the line that connects us, no matter how dazzling I am
I want to put it on TikTok, so can I do it one more time?
I'll just do the chorus one more time and put it on YouTube short and TikTok.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
If I could be a constellation with you
On a starry night, a fleeting wish
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle
Shaking, shaking, shaking, shaking, shaking, shaking, shaking, shaking, shaking, shaking
If I could gather with you and become a constellation
Tsuramiyage
Let's do it one more time
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
Phew.
If I could gather with you and become a constellation
On a starry night, a fleeting wish
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle
Trembling signals
If we could be constellations, gathered with you
I'd look up at the sky and point my finger at you
Don't break the line that connects us
No matter how bright I am
I'll make it through.
I'm gonna make it through with you... free, free, free.
I'm free and I'm free and I'm free and I'm free.
I'm gonna go to 8:00, but it's a good time, but it's not a good time.
All right, everyone, take a request.
Let's take a look at the requests and see what we can do.
The right hand is random.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
45 minutes is so short!
I thought 45 minutes was short.
Ooh.
Oh!
Oh.
Are you done with work today? Yeah, I am.
I'm more nervous than I thought I'd be. Here we go.
What? Five more minutes... until 9:30!
Haru said 9:45 on her own.
Haru said 9:30, right? That's right! That's right!
Until 9:35, right? What? Is that a specific time?
Is this time-specific?
Does YouTube have a time limit?
Oh, that's right!
Then let's extend TikTok by 5 minutes.
The chorus... would you prefer just the chorus?
Yes, I'd like to do Mr. Bish's orchestra.
Let's do it again. Can we do it again? Can we do it again?
I'll never forget the way we laughed when we held hands.
Oh, God, let's do it again.
It's hard.
I'll never forget the way we held hands and laughed.
I'll never forget the tears we cried, the voices we talked to, the orchestra
I'll never forget the voice that said goodbye
I thought we were so close, but now the only connection we have is that sky
I can do it!
I don't know! I'll try! I'll try! Okay, let's see.
I'll try to make it till about 9:35.
I'll be very selective.
I'm pretty sure this search is taking a while. I'll try to remember it.
But if I tell you, you'll really have to memorize it.
I'll try my best.
Help me with the search...
Yeah, help me with the search...
I can't talk while I'm typing.
I've recently learned this.
Oh, my stomach's a little upset.
My stomach is getting upset.
I've been told I'm not very good at this.
You're so random.
Are you okay? It's just...
It's crazy.
I got a commemorative crown, but...
Thank you so much for your hard work.Good luck and thank you for your help, earnestly.
Okay, so I recently learned.
Kit Standard.
I'm sure I'm a standard girl.
I'm mediocre.
I can't be your hinoy.
To you.
I don't know what kind of person I am
I have no idea what I'm like
Inside and out, I'm ordinary
As soon as we're done talking
You're always going away
Do you know my first name?
I wonder if she even knows my first name.
I've been staring at you... every time I find myself looking for you.
I've been looking for that voice
I wonder if you can reach me, or if you can't
I don't care if it reaches you or not
I'm just an ordinary person by any standard
I'll never be one of you
I'll always be a sphere, and I can't stay like this
Even though it's my absolute destiny
I want you, I want you, I want you
If it's just my feelings for you, I'll get a perfect score
I can't help thinking that I'm not good enough for you
It's because you're so wonderful
Thank you for watching!
I heard that we've crossed the 30-minute barrier.
Well, it's getting a little sad, so I'd like to end on a lighter note.
I wish we could have done more. We'll do it again.
I'll do it again.
I can do this one too. I can do this too. I can do Lion Girl.
Lion Girl is difficult, surprisingly. Then I'd like to end on a bright note. I'll stay in the red section.
Se-no de
Go!
Tomorrow for the rest of your life.
Tomorrow for the rest of my life
Even the best day is the best day.
Oh, no, no, definitely not.
Good job, guys.
Tomorrow will be a better day
Or fall in love with destiny
Or a stream of dreams will come true
You can do whatever you want.
It's not true, but I'm sure.
Hey, you know what?
Oh, that was hard!
I don't know. Where was I?
Oh, oh, oh...
Oh, that was hard. What? Why did I think I could do this?
Let's do iSong. iSong is better.
It's so much, so much, so much freedom. What should I do?
I'm going to get in trouble with my mom. I'm sure she'll be furious with me.
She'll say, "You should do it after you finish it more.
But what? I was practicing when Mom wasn't around.
Yeah, she says that a lot.
I can do iSong better.
Mom, please forgive him.
Tell your mom, guys. Here, tell Mom.
I love you.
Cue me.
I love you, too.
I'm going to be a little bit selfish.
I promised you I'd make you happy, so be prepared
I want to take you further and further and further and further and further
I want you to be in the air even more
Wherever you go, I'll be there
I'll make you smile, I'll make you smile, I'll make you smile
I want you to tell me how many times I love you morning, noon and night every day
Look at me, I want Whatever the time, I need you Don't talk to any other girls
I want to be pretty, don't you? Then don't spare me
Someone else I couldn't scroll past. Someone else can have me?
Can I put my head in the sand? Feel it. I want, you know?
You know what love is, don't you? I want you more than anyone
I love you more than anyone
I want you to know I want you to know I want you to know I want you to know I want you to know I want you to know I want you to know I want you to know I want you to know I want you to know I want you to know I want you to know I want you to know I want you to know I want you to know I want you to know I want you to know I want you to know I want you to know
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes no.
Yes, yes, yes.
Can you sing them all? Thank you.
So, it's been a bit of a slow delivery, but...
Well, we'll do it again next time.
Thank you very much for 10,000 subscribers!
I'll do my best on YouTube.
I'll do my best on YouTube, so please come back and watch again!
Thank you so much for enjoying my channel.
Bye bye.
Scooch over.
Thank you. See you soon.
Please promote me to your friends.
Thank you.
See you soon. Bye bye.